me where do I [__] there in the woods in
the woods all you need to stay warm is a
warm body and a blanket I promise you
yeah man you just draw your curs up like
this it's night time I'll show you
exactly how this
works on one
second take these out hey how homegrown
does it
get so come here Logan a little remote
back here a little display go get on you
hit the
button all right everything's on this is
nice yeah see uh everything is working
right now you know you got your VIN
fanid where do you
[__] well me where do I [__] be in the
woods in the woods yeah I don't want to
carry it around with me but if I'm in a
Walmart parking lot or something you
know we have a full bathroom right
here
yeah it has a shower look hey for a
little more little more Elbow Room if
you need it
um that's the thing man when you live in
a van you rarely use this [__] but it's
very important to have for the few times
that you do so I got a little two burer
gas stove um I have this is a air
conditioner heater combination um so now
need two4 it's 120 and as you see it
it's running right now um here I'll show
you since you're so here's my
app right
now
2 we've had the fridge on for days eight
amps M so it's pulling right now 8
Amp that's on AC right and now when I
turn it off right I mean that's just
it's just running right now but now you
see it drop off okay but see the coolest
thing thing is is I can do this I can
cut that inverter off it uses no
energy and I can cut the fridge on cuz
it's running off a DC cuz it costs 4
amps just to run the inverter right I've
designed this thing pretty well I have a
lot of functionality this pulls out you
know you can sit right there this breaks
down if you and I want to go somewhere
no homo this is two beds one bed two bed
really uhhuh I have a Walmart cooler
that I bought randomly that fits under
there perfectly I didn't even know uh
Alex and I use it like this because we
use no
heat we like we probably used the heater
maybe five six times total and most of
that was when we were in Iowa in January
how many amps do it pull when you used
the heat well here's the thing you don't
need the heat all you need to stay warm
is a warm body and a blanket I promise
you and it is the best feeling on planet
Earth to wake up and have a cold face
and a warm body I'm not lying to you
where's your starlink at I don't have it
on right now I don't need it here
it's it's all detached no it goes on the
roof mount okay um you have SP pretty
cool hey so hey so look [__] awesome
I have this little table right here if I
want you know the beds are split I made
that little table and it bolts in right
here so if I want to have a a proper
dinner I can
um then right here check this out this
is my office
I tell you step into my
office hiking
stick so you
take this little
[Music]
table clip it in like
that you can slide it up to get in and
out and then slide it back where you
need my man [__] [__] D yeah so we
have these little
foils right when you park somewhere
you just take
these little
[Music]
buttons [__] and you pop them in like
this you put you put button hey hold on
watch out
dog you
[Music]
pright [__] yeah man you just draw
your curs up like this and it's night
time man uh so we really use the the
propane heater you know you just I'll
set this to what I want it to be and uh
like if I I'll set this on 70 and I'll
leave it on and then I'll just cut the
inverter off and I'll reach over with my
toe in the morning and hit that [__]
with my toe and it'll cut on it'll turn
the house on and this will be already on
and so to cut on and about 6 minutes
you're good this [__] is
65° yeah but man really in Van life this
is what a a normal day looks like bro
Alex and I are in this van and really we
stay in there at night you know and it's
chilly at night in the 50s out there in
the PMW so we wake up under a warm
blanket and we usually [__] every
morning on the mobile internet do
whatever little bit of work you got to
do or [__] off and then we go for a
trail run oh yeah um and come back from
a trail run pop a beer cook some food
usually you know great fruit [__] you
know some fruit and usually a couple
eggs avocado man I eat really low to the
ground um things that that can't that
don't need
Refrigeration like my grandpa didn't use
a refrigerator hardly you think about
this guys we've lived like this for so
long now we have all this [__] [__]
that you do not need and when you cut it
out of your life you have less [__] to
keep up with so you can have a lot more
fun like bro we just you don't have to
refrigerate cheese this should be good
for a week right down that counter
eggs butter that's what I'm saying now
now if you if you kill a deer unless you
have smoked meat dude I eat a lot of
fresh fish and I eat a ton of smoked
fish but like I know you eat I eat yeah
I eat low to the ground man I eat very
basic um and so we'll we'll go for a
trail run and come back and take a cold
Plunge in an ice cold River and it sucks
but I'm going to tell you you get in
there and you rinse off and then you get
out and you sit on a [__] rock in the
Sun and you dry off and when you get
done is
dude it's a sungasm I can't tell you
what it feels like you you're warm and
tingly from head to toe and then you
drink another beer and smoke a blunt and
get in the van together and you know
what we do we just drive we don't have
an atlas there's no sell it it doesn't
matter where you go it does not [__]
matter so you just go oh that looks cool
and so you just pull off wherever you
want this is my solar generator in him
so what I have right here is pretty
big this is I think the fourth build the
fourth gen there's a few prototypes that
that we went through the lights the only
thing that runs AC in here is the
microwave the outlets and the the air
conditioner a heater if you use it0 yeah